wiris.com 2019-08-04

# Privacy Policy | WIRIS | math & science

_Version 1.3_  
_June 25, 2019_

## Terms of use

Check the terms of use of this page at [www.wiris.com/en/legal-advice](http://www.wiris.com/en/legal-advice)

## What does this policy cover

This Privacy Policy covers the information we collect about you when you use our products, services and websites. We refer to our products, services and websites as "Services" in this policy. This policy also explains your choices about how we use information about you. Your choices include how you can object to certain uses of information about you and how you can access and update certain information about you. If you do not agree with this policy, do not access or use our Services.

## What information we collect about you

We collect information about you when you provide it to us and when you use our Services.

### Information you provide us

We collect information about you when you input it into the Services or otherwise provide it directly to us.

**Content you provide through our websites and store:  **  
If you buy our products you need to register so we can deliver them to you. We collect some necessary personal data and billing information for this purpose, and optionally your consent to receive newsletters from our Services. Payment information is managed by leading secure payment processing providers. You can find their privacy policies here: [Stripe Privacy Policy](https://stripe.com/es/privacy) and [Sage Pay Privacy Policy](https://www.sagepay.co.uk/policies/privacy-policy). 

**Information you provide through Wiris Quizzes Certification and Campus:**  
If you want to certificate with us your understanding and effective use of Wiris Quizzes you will be asked to register in a specific course in a Moodle administered by WIRIS. We collect the necessary personal data to register you as a user, as well as all the data you decide to add, including your answers and marks. 

**Content you provide through our products:**  
Some of our products will ask you for your license so we can use the fully features. Some of our products will also ask you for contact details so we can send you marketing information if you give us your consent.

**Information you provide through our support channels:**  
You may choose to submit information regarding a question or a problem you are experiencing with a Service to our support channels. You will be asked to provide contact information, a summary of the problem you are experiencing, and any other documentation, screenshots or information that would be helpful in resolving the issue.

### Information we collect automatically when you use the Services

We collect information about you when you use our Services, including using our products, browsing our websites, or asking for support.

**Content you provide through our products and demos:**  
Our services record certain requests and transactions in log files and in our cloud service. We record your IP, referrer metadata and other usage statistics. This log data is used for operating our Services, troubleshooting, statistics, analytics, quality assurance, and to monitor system security and can be analyzed to that end. We can publish anonymous statistics under the condition that no personally identifiable information can be derived from such statistics.

**Content you provide through our websites and store:**  
When you visit specific pages from our websites, we collect anonymous data about your interaction so we can improve content and our usability issues.

If you feel uncomfortable with these recordings, you can opt-out from being tracked here: [opt-out from tracking](https://www.hotjar.com/legal/compliance/opt-out).

_Cookies:_  
A “cookie” is a small piece of information that is sent by a web server to be stored on a web browser, so that it can later be read back from that browser the next time this unique visitor returns to that web server. This becomes useful for having the browser remember specific information about this visitor like location of their last visit, time spent, or user preferences (like style sheets). The cookie is a text file that is saved in the browser’s directory and is stored in RAM while the browser is running. Also, the cookie may be stored on the computer’s hard drive once you log off from that web site or web server.

We use a number of different cookies on our site. If you do not know what cookies are, or how to control or delete them, then we recommend you visit [http://www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) for detailed guidance.

The list below describes the cookies we use on this site and what we use them for. Currently we operate an ‘implied consent’ policy which means that we assume you are happy with this usage. If you are not happy, then you should either not use this site, or you should delete the cookies having visited the site, or you should browse the site using your browser’s anonymous usage setting (called “Incognito” in Chrome, “InPrivate” for Internet Explorer, “Private Browsing” in Firefox and Safari etc.).

These are cookies that are set by this website directly.

  * Google Analytics:  
We use Google Analytics to collect information about visitor behaviour on our website. Google Analytics stores information about what pages you visit, how long you are on the site, how you got here and what you click on. This Analytics data is collected via a JavaScript tag in the pages of our site and is not tied to personally identifiable information. We therefore do not collect or store your personal information (e.g. your name or address) so this information cannot be used to identify who you are.

You can find out more about Google’s position on privacy as regards its analytics service at <https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites>

  * Hotjar:  
[Hotjar](https://www.hotjar.com/) is a technology service that helps us better understand our users experience (e.g. how much time they spend on which pages, which links they choose to click, what users do and don’t like, etc.) and this enables us to build and maintain our service with user feedback. Hotjar uses cookies and other technologies to collect data on our users’ behavior and their devices (in particular device's IP address (captured and stored only in anonymized form), device screen size, device type (unique device identifiers), browser information, geographic location (country only), preferred language used to display our website). Hotjar stores this information in a pseudonymized user profile. Neither Hotjar nor we will ever use this information to identify individual users or to match it with further data on an individual user. For further details, please see Hotjar’s privacy policy by clicking on this [link](https://www.hotjar.com/legal/policies/privacy).   
You can opt-out to the creation of a user profile, Hotjar’s storing of data about your usage of our site and Hotjar’s use of tracking cookies on other websites by following this [opt-out link](https://www.hotjar.com/legal/compliance/opt-out).” 

## How we use information we collect

We collect and process information about you only where we have legal bases for doing so under applicable EU laws. The legal bases depend on the Services you use and how you use them. This means we collect and use your information only when:

  * We need it to provide you the Services, including to operate the Services and provide customer support;
  * It satisfies a legitimate interest (which is not overridden by your data protection interests), such as for license control, troubleshooting, statistics, analytics, quality assurance, and to monitor system security;
  * You give us consent to do so for a specific purpose. We only request consent for marketing communications.

If you have consented to our use of information about you for a specific purpose, you have the right to change your mind at any time, but this will not affect any processing that has already taken place. Where we are using your information because we have a legitimate interest to do so, you have the right to object to that use though, in some cases, this may mean no longer using the Services.

## How we don't share information we collect

We don’t share the information we collect about you with third parties. We are not in the business of selling information about you to advertisers or other third parties.

## How we store and secure information we collect

### Information storage and security

We use Amazon and Google data hosting service providers to host the information we collect automatically when you use the Services. The information you provide to us for marketing and support purposes is managed by leading Support Ticketing (ZenDesk) and Customer Relationship Manager (SalesForce) systems. All of them ensure the confidentiality and integrity of data with industry best practices.

### How long we keep information

How long we keep information we collect about you depends on the type of information, as described in further detail below. After such time, we will delete your information.

**Marketing information:**  
We retain information about your marketing preferences for a reasonable period of time from the date you last expressed interest in our Services.

**Wiris Quizzes Certification and Campus:**  
We retain your user account in our Moodle and all the content you decided to add for a reasonable period of time from the date you finished your certification.

**Any other information:**  
Our services record certain requests and transactions in log files and in our cloud service. We retain these logs for a reasonable period of time in terms of its needs of analysis depending on their purpose: troubleshooting, statistics, analytics, quality assurance, monitor system security…

## How to access and control your information

You have certain choices available to you when it comes to your information. Below is a summary of those choices, how to exercise them and any limitations.

### Your Choices

You have the right to request a copy of your information, to object to our use of your information, or to request the deletion or restriction of your information. You can exercise your right contacting us as provided in the Contact Us section below to request assistance. For specific information, you can also exercise your right as explained below.

Your request and choices may be limited in certain cases: for example if you ask to delete information which we are permitted by law or have compelling legitimate interests to keep. This applies, for example, to information we collected automatically when you used the services. If you have unresolved concerns, you may have the right to complain to a data protection authority in the country where you live, where you work or where you feel your rights were infringed.

**User account in our websites:**  
You can easily modify or delete your user account from the website. You just have to login and click on Delete or Modify. You can also contact us as provided in the Contact Us section below. Information you provided through

**Wiris Quizzes Certification and Campus:**  
You can modify or completely delete your user account and all the related content in Wiris Quizzes Certification and Campus just by contacting us as provided in the Contact Us section below.

**Contact details for marketing communications:**  
You may opt out of receiving marketing communications from us by using the unsubscribe link within each email or by contacting us as provided below to have your contact information removed from our promotional email list or registration database. You can update your information contacting us as provided in the Contact Us section below.

**Any other information you provided us:**  
Contact us as provided in the Contact Us section below.

## Updating your Information

At any time, you have the right to access, modify or request deletion of the information we have about you, by contacting us at support@wiris.com, or the address stated below:

Maths for More S.L.  
Muntaner 262  
08021 Barcelona  
SPAIN

## Amendments to Privacy Policy

Please note this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We expect most such changes to be minor, but there may be changes that are more significant. We will post those changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will also provide a more prominent notice or inform you by e-mail. Each version will be noted at the top of the page.

## Addendums

  * [MathType Privacy Policy](http://www.wiris.com/mathtype/privacy-policy). Details about what information we collect and how we use that information for MathType users.
  * [Wiris Quizzes Privacy Policy](http://www.wiris.com/en/quizzes/privacy-policy). Details about what information we collect and how we use that information for Wiris Quizzes users.
